If you want her, you'll have to use
your dual blades to take her from us.
If you can defeat me in combat,
you'll be free to take Asuna.
On the other hand, if you lose, you
will join the Knights of the Blood Oath.
Yeah, okay.
If you want to settle this
with swords, that's fine by me.
We'll have ourselves a duel then.
Better hurry, folks!
The good seats are going fast! Who's next?
My god!
You're such an idiot!
How could you agree to a duel?
Okay, calm down. I'm sorry.
It's not like you gave
me any other choice.
The other day, when you used
your duel wielding skill,
I've never seen anything like that before.
Thing is, the commander has
his own unique skill, too.
I know I've seen it a
bunch of times myself
the divine blade it
maximizes his offensive and
defensive moves his
attack is strong but his
defense is incredible
no one's ever seen the
commander's HP bar dipped
down into the yellow
zone before his invincibility
is way beyond the
normal game balance I
know what if you lose I
don't care if I don't
get my leave of absence?
I care about you having to join
the Knights of the Blood Oath.
Well, I'm not planning on losing easily.
I'm afraid of the fear of the past,
but I'm afraid of the future.
I'm afraid of the future.
This is my heart,
and I'm afraid of the future.
I'm sorry about this Kirito.
I didn't think this
would be such a big deal.
This is crazy.
Maybe I can get a cut of the tickets?
No.
But when we're finished, you'll become
an official member of the Guild.
I'll consider this your first mission.
Your shield?
Your reaction time is very impressive.
Yeah, and your defense is impregnable.
Not yet!
Give it time!
Be careful.
Now's my chance!
Ah!
Ruben! Ruben!
Uh, don't you guys have
uniforms that aren't so flashy?
Actually, that's one of
our less flashy ones.
You look great!
I'm in a guild.
I guess it's sort of my fault, isn't it?
No, this is a good opportunity.
As a solo player, I got
as far as I could go.
That makes me feel a little better.
Hey, Kirito? Hm?
Why do you avoid guilds?
And people?
I hope you don't mind my asking.
I mean,
it's not because you're a beta tester or
because you have unique skills, is it?
You do care about people.
It was a long time ago.
About a year or so.
Up to now, that was the
only guild I was in.
It was small.
Including me, there were six of us in it.
They called themselves
the Moonlit Black Cats.
As players, they were good, but their
levels were way lower than mine.
And I thought if I told them what my level
was, they wouldn't have wanted me around.
So I decided to keep
my mouth shut about it.
And I joined up with them.
I'd watch them,
messing around, having fun, and I
guess I wanted to be part of that too.
Then one day...
I'm the reason the whole
guild was wiped out.
If I hadn't hidden the
fact that I was a beater,
I could have convinced them how
dangerous that trap really was.
I killed them.
Sachi.
All of them.
I'm not gonna die, got that?
I can't die because
I have to protect you.
I got a train. That's right.
You, me, and one other guy
are going to form a party.
Then, we're all going to go
clear the dungeon on this floor.
Hold on, Godfrey.
Kirito and I are already in...
I can't do anything about it, ma 'am.
Besides, as second-in-command, you
know we can't ignore the rules.
If he's going to be joining us,
then it's my job as
commander of the front lines
to take the kid out and
evaluate his skills.
But that's ridiculous.
He doesn't need evaluation.
He's stronger than you.
Kid, in 30 minutes, I want to
see you at the Western Gate.
Hoorah!
We finally had a chance to be alone.
I'll be back soon.
Think he can wait for me?
Mm-hmm.
Just be careful.
Hey, kid!
We're waiting for you!
Are you serious?
Yep.
Look at it this way.
We're all on the same guild,
so I figured now's a good time as
any for you guys to bury the hatchet.
About the other day, I
apologized for my behavior.
I was rude to you, and I...
I promise it won't happen again.
Yeah, sure.
All right, ladies, time to focus.
Today, I'll be checking out how
you react to dangerous situations.
So, I'm going to need you to hand
over all the crystals in your storage.
Even my teleport crystals? Mm-hmm.
Yeah, okay.
Awesome.
Now, let's go clear a dungeon!
Yay.
This looks like a good
place to take a break.
Ciao time, ladies.
Say ah!
We've been poisoned.
What the hell's going on?
You packed the water, Kuradeel.
What'd you do?
You bastard.
Antidote crystals, hurry!
Poor, sad old Godfrey.
I always knew you were a colossal idiot,
but this proves you're
even dumber than I thought.
Don't do this!
No, stop it!
Here's my plan.
Our party was walking along when...
We were attacked by this gang of criminal
players who appeared out of nowhere.
You both fought hard, but
you were killed in battle.
It was just me against all of them.
And somehow, I courageously and
single-handedly We fucked them all off!
You know, I just killed an
innocent bystander because of you.
How am I going to live with myself?
From over here, you look like
you're having a blast doing it.
Why the hell would a guy like you
join the Knights of the Blood Oath?
You'd be more at home with
one of the criminal guilds.
What an interesting observation.
You have sharp eyes.
You're with Leafa and Coffin.
The murder killed.
That's where I got the skills
to paralyze bastards like you.
Where's my head?
I better stop talking or
the poison will wear off.
And we wouldn't want that.
Time to finish you off for good.
The poison's not wearing off.
How's it feel?
Come on.
I want to know how it feels knowing
you're about to die like a dog.
What?
Is your tongue paralyzed too?
Is this it?
Is this where I'm gonna die?
Come on now!
It's your last chance to say something.
You really are going to die.
Why do you keep struggling?
Are you afraid of dying after all?
No, I'm just not ready yet.
Is that so?
That's the way I like it!
Die!
I made it.
I made it in time.
Thank God.
I made it.
I was tracking your position
on the map the whole time,
and then I saw Godfrey disappear.
here.
I got worried something happened.
But you're alive.
I'm not dreaming, am I?
No.
You're not.
Hang on.
I'll finish this.
Hasuna, I can explain everything.
We were just training when all
of a sudden there was this...
Damn you!
I give up! I surrender!
Please don't kill me!
I'll leave the guild!
You'll never see me again, I promise!
Please!
I don't want to die!
The oldest trick in the book!
And you fell for it, bitch!
God damn you.
You murdered me.
I'm sorry.
This was all my fault, wasn't it?
I'm sorry,
but I should stay away
from you for your sake.
Asuna, my life belongs to you.
I'll give it up for you.
I want to stay with you until the end.
And I promise I'll do
anything to protect you, too.
Forever.
No matter what.
I swear.
I'll do everything I can to make
sure you get back to the real world.
Asuna, could I?
Stay with you for the night?
Okay.
What are you waiting for? Get undressed.
Don't just sit there it's embarrassing
no wait I didn't I mean I just all I
wanted was to spend the night with you
tonight and not the the other thing. Huh?
You...
you...
You dummy!
Hey what you smiling about I was
just having a dream about my old life?
It was weird and the
dream I had everything in
aincrad everything that
happened in meeting you was
just that a dream and I
was so scared but it wasn't
thank god it wasn't now
that That sounds weird.
Don't you want to go back?
Of course I do.
I do, it's just...
I don't want my life
here to disappear is all.
The last two years have
been very special to me.
I realize that now.
Listen, Kirito.
I was thinking, maybe we could leave
the front lines for a while. What?
I'm scared.
I feel like if we return
to the battlefield now,
something bad's going to happen again.
Or maybe I'm just tired of it all.
I know what you mean.
I guess I am too.
In the southwest of Floor 22,
there's this tiny little
village by a lake and a forest.
We could get a house together.
And then...
And then what?
Then, we get married.
Okay.
I heard a little bit of money,
but it's a little bit of money.
I've heard a little bit of money,
Just to repeat the fact
that the reality is.
I've been waiting for a few years.
I've found the future to
be able to see the future.
I've never seen this dream.
Next time the girl of morning dew?